https://nantgwrtheyrn.org/privacy-policy/

The latest regarding coronavirus (COVID-19)
LearnStayTasteShopCelebrateMeetDiscoverMore AboutTimelineNewsBlogsContact
CymraegWebsite Privacy PolicyNant Gwrtheyrn Welsh Language and Heritage Centre is committed to maintaining customer privacy and maintaining the security of any personal data which we receive from you.Nant Gwrtheyrn Welsh Language and Heritage Centre is committed to responsible data management and subscribes to the principles of data protection legislation in the United Kingdom.The policy: This privacy policy is for this website and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it. It explains how we comply with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), the DPA (Data Protection Act) and the PECR (Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations).This policy will explain areas of this website that may affect your privacy and personal details, how we process, collect, manage and store those details and how your rights under the GDPR, DPA & PECR are adhered to. Additionally, it will explain the use of cookies or software, advertising or commercial sponsorship from third parties and the download of any documents, files or software made available to you (if any) on this website. Further explanations may be provided for specific pages or features of this website in order to help you understand how we, this website and its third parties (if any) interact with you and your computer/device in order to serve it to you. Our contact information is provided if you have any questions.The DPA & GDPR May 2018We and this website complies with the DPA (Data Protection Act 1998) and already complies with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) which comes into effect from May 2018. We will update this policy accordingly after the completion of the UK’s exit from the European Union.Use of CookiesThis website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Cookies are used to track the contents of your shopping cart if you choose to purchase products or courses. As required by legislation, where applicable this website uses a cookie control system, allowing the user to give explicit permission or to deny the use of/saving of cookies on their computer/device.What are cookies?
Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors or use the cookie control system if available upon their first visit.Website Visitor TrackingThis website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.Downloads & Media FilesAny downloadable documents, files or media made available on this website are provided to users at their own risk. While all precautions have been undertaken to ensure only genuine downloads are available users are advised to verify their authenticity using third party anti virus software or similar applications.We accept no responsibility for third party downloads and downloads provided by external third party websites and advise users to verify their authenticity using third party anti-virus software or similar applications.Contact & Communication With usUsers contacting this us through this website do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use.Visitors that purchase, promote or use our products will be asked to enter basic personal information. This information collected on our database is not available for sale and use by third parties, beyond the essential requirement for credit card validation during purchase. The information is used solely for our billing and payment purposes, and notifying customers of future updates to our products or services.Where we have clearly stated and made you aware of the fact, and where you have given your express permission, we may use your details to send you products/services information through a mailing list system. This is done in accordance with the regulations named in ‘The policy’ above.Email Mailing List & Marketing MessagesWe operate an email mailing list program, used to inform subscribers about products, services and/or news we supply/publish. Users can subscribe through an online automated process where they have given their explicit permission. Subscriber personal details are collected, processed, managed and stored in accordance with the regulations named in ‘The policy’ above. Subscribers can unsubscribe at any time through an automated online service, or if not available, other means as detailed in the footer of sent marketing messages (or unsubscribe from all Mailchimp lists). The type and content of marketing messages subscribers receive, and if it may contain third party content, is clearly outlined at the point of subscription.Email marketing messages may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of subscriber data relating to engagement, geographic, demographics and already stored subscriber data.Our EMS (email marketing service) provider is; MailChimp and you can read their privacy policy in the resources section.External Website Links & Third PartiesAlthough we only look to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text/banner/image links to other websites)We cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite our best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and we cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.Social Media Policy & UsageWe adopt a Social Media Policy to ensure our business and our staff conduct themselves accordingly online. While we may have official profiles on social media platforms users are advised to verify the authenticity of such profiles before engaging with, or sharing information with such profiles. We will never ask for user passwords or personal details on social media platforms. Users are advised to conduct themselves appropriately when engaging with us on social media.There may be instances where our website features social sharing buttons, which help share web content directly from web pages to the respective social media platforms. You use social sharing buttons at your own discretion and accept that doing so may publish content to your social media profile feed or page. You can find further information about some social media privacy and usage policies in the resources section below.Privacy Policy ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time. You are advised to review this privacy policy periodically for any changes. This Privacy Policy was last modified on May 25, 2018.Resources & Further InformationOverview of the GDPR – General Data Protection RegulationData Protection Act 1998Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003The Guide to the PECR 2003Twitter Privacy PolicyFacebook Privacy PolicyGoogle Privacy PolicyLinkedin Privacy PolicyMailChimp Privacy PolicySearch
Recent News and Blogs
Work Welsh returns in new format for 2021
The language teacher who became the student by Theresa Munford
Celebrate at Nant GwrtherynUseful LinksNewsBlogsEventsShopCareers and JobsTerms & Conditions
CookiesWe use cookies to allow us to better understand how the site is used. By continuing to use this site, you consent to this policy. Click to learn moreOkay, thanks
